Guide to the Allan F. Jones' Pitt Football Team Photograph Collection, 1922 UA.9.10.F
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Allan F. Jones' Pitt Football Team Photograph Collection
1922
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Jones, Allan F.
UA.9.10.F
0.25 Linear Feet (1 half box)
This collection consists of 42 photographs of the 1922 University of Pittsburgh football team and include photographs of Coach Pop Warner, individual players, and groups. Digital reproductions of this collection are available online.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of the collection are available online as part of the University of Pittsburgh Historic Photographs collection.
Previous Citation
Allan F. Jones' Pitt Football Team Photograph Collection, 1922, UA.9.10.F, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Acquisition Information
Gift of Fran L. and John Everett Jones, the grandchildren of Allan F. Jones, on April 18, 2011.
Scope and Content Notes
These photographs were taken by Allan F. Jones in the early 1920s and are believed to be from the 1922 summer football training camp. Two photographs are of Head Coach Glenn Scobey "Pop" Warner, who coached the Pitt Panthers from 1915-1923. Identified players include: Nicholas Schuler, Edward "Ned" Newbaker, JC Winterburn, Marsh Johnson, Milo Gwosden, John E. "Tiny" Miller, Edward J. "Ned" Ashbaugh, and Frank W. "Pie" Williams.
Football coaches -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sports; Football players -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Photographs; University of Pittsburgh; Football -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Warner, Glenn S. (Glenn Scobey) -- Photographs; Pitt Panthers (Football team) -- Photographs; University of Pittsburgh -- Football
- Glenn Scobey "Pop" Warner, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Allan Jones, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Doc" Weidle, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Edward J. "Ned" Newbaker, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Field Shots, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- J. Charles Winterburn, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- John E. "Tiny" Miller, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Johnny", 1922 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Marsh Johnson, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Milo Gwosden, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Nicholas Schuler, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- "Tommy" and Alec Stevenson (Tommy's father) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Group Pictures, 1922; Individuals identified: "Tommy," Allan F. Jones, Marsh Johnson, Nick Schuler, Frank "Pie" Williams, JC Winterburn, Milo Gwosden, Ned Newbaker, William D. Ashbaugh, (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Unidentified, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 14)